Hello, welcome to this episode of Learn German in Hindi.
Today we are going to learn only 10
words. How many are there? Only 10
and with that word we are going to learn 10 new conjunctions
and we are going to learn 10 ways to join two sentences. It
is interesting.
For that, it is important that our
basic conjunction culture of
mobile van Tulsi, its episode number is
22, should be clear to you. If it is not, then
check it and let it be clear. So today
we have to learn only 1098, what does it mean? Why did we
learn it there? I drank because I liked drinking.
What did we do? Do
you remember
what we said in this love story? Take the
character which will come in the middle and the
moving square which is going to go at the end. This
cross is clear. So today it is very simple
that when we have learnt 10 connectors,
I have given 10 questions in the description below.
Try to solve them, their
answers are also given below them, then
you will know that you  I want to know if she has come to understand this
or not, so let's start
learning all the conjunctions. The first one is my favorite,
Dante Dance, meaning it will be in Hindi and English.
Seeing the diner from Chandi, they must learn
German. They like the launch of the mission.
If I say that I think that also must learn
German.
Shoaib had put this tender. The tanker
Raj, after watching the video, why did he go to the lunar mission end? So,
till this conditional class, you remember this day's
Das, otherwise the chairman, he understood, he liked acting a little more.
Now the opinion that is must learn
German, French is this month's Dayak
Jaihe Layer Mission and argues
that he wants German in this role Gurung's Baba. In
this way, Avdhesh Das, Veer, Veer Das,
Mikram can do very well. All these
Chinese have gone to this bank and village. This winner - Mother still have been
stopped from this. Or you
can use it and your sentence becomes
of a completely different level. This will be
very useful for you in special exams and the basic working is very
simple.  Laddu is the one that was going to run, you will get it at the
end, nothing to do but at a
high level plug a villain from the central
when you listen to this you ask a question yes
no question means do you know what is in the list
fill this marking
how will this marking be done in the backlink animal ist mark
in bearing service now we do it a little bit differently I want to know its
mark that on which we will take now
what did we do in English we have put it so
why did we put it why was it indirect speech
when we also say weather and want to know weather
marking throughout the day it is for that in German so
what will happen look this minister mission
Om mark in be reduced it's just and
simple Om means weather in English
he used to use Sanjay Dutt
a similar third character that is Bigg
Boss question ok love you stay questions
means what is that Wwe Raju you ask in English then
we have learnt it in less detail
ride so if you want to ask which is how
much cost cost how much cost  So what is the cost of
BPL card status VPN
status Okay now in English if you have to ask can you
please tell me how much did it cost
if you see when you were making a normal sentence
you had put that I think that
university German date connect that is this was the
question then you put your effigy of weather I want to know
this market zinc unique and on this
when you added two things from your debit to the question
you did not put any collector
because the next question is its
effects of bus conductor can you please tell me how much
Dravid's of floor cost year
everyone can answer exactly in German also if you
use w10 question then the vote de
question itself will correct such a connect you do
not need to use different connects
only unknown direction condom registrar server will
go to the bank so
what will happen to the status of VPN of classical channel seniors if
corner we less cost only that student
got but how heavy has the call center become how it
seems that Anant Singh is where money
VCCus cost and again  Very useful in
exam, by the way if he is telling you that
he is the one who deserves it, then what will you say normal, he is the one who
deserves it, as this this
program got a tadka, how am I, it was his
birthday, where is Sanjay, very simple, so these
three connectors which are canter, indirect
speech record, which Das and Delhi
admission, now we will learn two more collectors which are
simple, so first of all Ranbir and I
mean during exam, I don't use it much, I
mean I don't talk, the van driver is
driving, so I will not keep talking, so what will happen,
look at this red, next Veronica, on this
this red list Veronica pimples and like
you should know this for during
and there is a conductor who does not use it, then we will
learn Pal Pal, I mean
if he is not there, then what will happen,
my play, I will not play, I will play
in a serious note, so what will happen, this Vansh
villain, Ishwar appeal, unfair net speed, speed, it will just be
fun, that something very simple, now send this
important one message, make it a little
simple, you are going to become important, so
Important 130 potatoes If any incident happens near you
which generally happens only once then
click on it that when I was 10 years old I learned
English when I was 15 years old
I learned to ride a scooter so this is
used for them that the pattern will
remain so let's see English years old when
strangers are there then
what will happen this week English glue all
Yudhishthir friend Alto is car paint second
sentence normally Ishwar out of that channel
also oh wow very simple side now let's
take a simple C B4 B4 B4 is said in German
and is said to doctor and a
simple English if you have to say milk so that's why then what will you
say so
a spring commission before sleep very simple
just like it was in English now here there are
two these words so that varma
mendak you can do it in reverse no tension
so after iodine milk I sleep after
iodine then what will happen this loop
this flame na step this chilli this must be said
and owner would have been through Ichhawar chilli
What will happen with trunk milk, enter
Islam fruit, no step, this maximum tax, yes
without my simple, just like you use in English,
you will learn new words,
rate actor Sharman is a mistress, which is
not used much, there is an exam, how many times do
you use English, that
people who lang, so how does it work,
see that brother,
I will players on this place will play
along display, so what will happen this year, Pir
Westfield, please, if you want to do a little remedy, then
you will remember the dialogue from Sholay, as long as
your legs move,
rate sonth, this basically
after reduction, the dance of the decisions will right
click, hair long as you dance, so what will this
loop do to remove trans fat, loose the langar milk,
okay, now we see the last one,
which is again important,
so we started with regular, which is very important,
now we will do diabetes in the price, so that is
important, and Islam, what does
purifier mean, then what does stain remove, that
explains the purpose
Yes, say for example I eat fruits and vegetables
so that I can stay healthy I don't eat
fruits and vegetables should be added to
turmeric so what will happen is that we
normally break the mute the price of
this don't Blackburn price is a mid
level snake replace table
because this is the character till that is very
simple and there are total 10 types of character seats right now there is nothing in it
if you know how to
use oil then it will get you 10
awards okay only the top madam has gone
clear now see when you will remember
there also we had said that sometimes we
can also say like this that brother viral this oil
only their class you
can bring first so what am I in that the
former VC's cross brought first but the
first one which brought first that classification
first position that is why I have been
till control system in it so if you
told me more today while this
I your mother an additional relationship after that
Kamakhya Patrika came  Here also most of
the receiver which is before is all felt, it
comes in the first position like this, meaning today the disciple was
not able to understand the behavior, gestures, favorite 2 inches
air is the first thing after the English calendar com
when the first position works in the
second position, yes now they have this again
audition its rich list is clear
or before Islam and Priyanka Ishq
Mirch Priyanka is Mirch remember
personal category or Kumar that the first one which is
a glass is a first position next we are doing it, it
is very simple but if you have the basic
concept then today we will learn only 10 new words
and we have learned to join sentences in 10 ways, right
below this and
in the description I have given 10 more sentences,
you try to solve them, the
answers are given below them, then you will know
how clear your concept is, I
hope you have understood this connection,
we will meet in the next episode,
thank you